Now that we've done a lot of the heavy lifting,
完成很多复杂的流程之后
we're going to complete a few different functions
我们将编写几个不同的函数
that will allow us to use what we've done above,
并利用在上面获得的结果
to make recommendations for any user based on the users that are similar to one another,
根据相互关联的用户向任何用户推荐电影
and based on the movies that they haven't seen.
并且会推荐用户没有看过的电影
So we want to recommend new movies to users based on similar users,
我们将根据相似用户向用户推荐新电影
but that are movies that they haven't necessarily seen before.
但是推荐的是用户之前没有看过的电影
In order to do that, there's a bunch of functions down here.
下面有很多函数
So we want to get the closest neighbors.
我们想要获取最近邻
So we'll find the closest neighbors,
我们将找到最近邻
we'll get the movies that are liked,
并且将获取用户喜欢的电影
and there's a min rating portion to that will pull the movie names,
这里有个最低评分
and make those as recommendations.
我们将提取并推荐这些片名
Then we'll basically do that for all of our users.
然后对所有用户都采取这一流程
If you think about what we had here was,
我们在这里
we computed the Euclidean distance for each pair of users.
计算了每对用户的欧几里得距离
If we were to do that for every set of users,
这个存储的就是
that's basically what's stored in this.
每对用户的结果
So similar to the idea of having the two pairs of users
与针对两对用户
and then the correlation coefficient,
计算相关系数相似
this does the same thing but with distances,
但是这里使用的是距离
and therefore we don't have any names.
所以不会出现任何 NaN
If we look at this down below,
在下面
you can see we have User 1,
可以看到 user1 user2
User 2, and then the distance.
还有距离
So there's no distance between two users that are exactly the same.
两个完全一样的用户之间没有距离
But the smaller that distance,
距离越小
the more similar to those two users are.
两个用户越相似
So this Euclidean distance measure is probably
这个欧几里得距离衡量方法
a better measure than our correlation coefficient,
比我们的相关系数衡量方法更好
because it doesn't have any names.
因为它没有任何 NaN
So essentially, what we want to do is use that data frame,
我们将使用该 DataFrame
and basically pull the users who are most similar to that user.
提取出与该用户最相似的用户
So we want to sort this by the users
我们将按照与特定用户最相似的用户
that are most similar to a particular user.
对这个进行排序
So you can imagine subsetting,
这样就只查看
looking at only User 1 equal to 2,
用户 1 等于用户2 的情况
sorting the Euclidean distances from smallest to largest,
按照从小到大的顺序排列欧几里得距离
and then pulling the n highest,
然后提取出前 n 个值
and those would be the n most similar users.
也就是前 n 个相似用户
So we want to write a function that does that.
我们将编写一个函数
One way that we could do that is by going into that data frame,
一种方法是从该 DataFrame 中
pulling the user ones that are equal to our user.
提取出等于这个用户的用户
So you give me the user,
当你给我特定用户后
and I'm going to pull from that data frame only those individuals.
我将从该 DataFrame 中仅提取这些用户
Then I want to sort by the Euclidean distance column.
然后按照欧几里得距离列排序
So I'm going to sort these by, right.
所以按照这个排序
So if we look at what was brought back, I'm going to sort them by this.
看看这里返回的数据 将按照这个排序
So I'm going to only pull the parts of the data frame
我将仅从该 DataFrame 中
that are related to the user that you give me,
提取与你提供的用户相关的用户
and then I'm going to sort by this Euclidean distance.
然后按照欧几里得距离排序
Then essentially from there,
接下来
I just want to pull from the first individual
我将从第一个用户开始提取
because the top one is always going to be
因为最上面的始终是用户本身
the user themselves up through the end,
一直提取到最后
and I want a list of the User 2's.
获取 user2 列表
So this will be a list excluding the user themselves
这个列表排除了特定用户本身
and grabbing all of the users in a order in which they're closest.
并按照从近到远的顺序获取所有相似用户
So we can even test that out if we wanted to. Put this up here.
我们可以测试一下将这段代码放到这里
Let's say we want to find the closest neighbors to User 2 who we had above.
假设我们想要获取用户 2 的最近邻
Great. So basically, these are sorted from
Great这些值按照欧几里得距离
closest to farthest away in terms of Euclidean distance.
从近到远排序